# DAVID SORRELUZ

## **Digital Disruption**

+971 56 410 44 00

@ sorreluz@gmail.com

♥ United Arab Emirates

#### FIND ME ONLINE



LinkedIN DavidSorreluz



Skype DavidSorreluz

#### **MINDSET**

I believe technology has the power to change the world to a better place. For the last four years, I have been working on changing business's mindset into disrupting their own business and looking for a more open, digitized and transparent future.

## **INDUSTRY EXPERTISE**

Digital Innovation

Entering into new markets

Sales Development

**Growth Initiatives** 

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Enterprise Sales Manager

**Temenos** 

₩ 08/2018 - Ongoing

**♀** United Arab Emirates

Revolutionizing banking software

- · Responsible for managing seven accounts with a total of seven-figure revenue in Angola and Mozambique
- New sales development in Angola, Botswana, Cape Verde, Guinea-Bissau, Lesotho, Malawi, Mozambique, Namibia, São Tome and Principe, South Africa, Swaziland, Zambia and Zimbabwe

## **Business Development Executive**

Finastra

**1** 07/2017 - 08/2018

**♀** United Arab Emirates

**Financial Software Solutions** 

- · Achieved 135% of my sales quota, 100+ qualified leads, \$12m in value close won deals
- Some of my responsibilities were to prepare Go-To-Market plans and sales strategy; prospect potential clients conduct rigorous follow up to progress
- Implement and launch Campaigns and Events to ensure consistent pipeline creation and pipeline acceleration along the fiscal year;
- · Regions: Southern African Development Community, West Africa, East Africa, Southern Europe, South Asia and GCC

## Business Development Manager

**FittPass** 

**11/2016 - 05/2017** 

**9** United Arab Emirates

FittTech Startup that is disrupting the Fitness Industry

- Some of my responsibilities were researching and identifying sales opportunity, generating leads, target identification and classification, meeting the client, and hiring and training new employees
- Built new revenue stream from selling the platforms advantages to physical instructors and nutritionists

## THE COOL QUOTE

"The doers are the major thinkers. The people that really create the things that change this industry are both the thinker and doer in one person."

Steve Jobs

## **EDUCATION**

Digital Transformation: From AI and IOT to Cloud, Blockchain, and Cybersecurity

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

## 2019 - Ongoing

Post Graduation in Banking, Corporate, Finance and Securities Law

Institut de Formation Bancaire Luxembourg

Bachelor's Degree in Elementary **Education and Teaching** 

Universidade Lusófona de Humanidades e **Tecnologias** 

**2010 - 2014 ♀** Portugal

High School Diploma in Computer Programming and IT

Secondary School

**2005 - 2009 ♀** Portugal

#### **CERTIFICATION**

Digital Transformation (2019)

LinkedIn

Adaptive Project Leadership (2019)

LinkedIn

Marketing in a Digital World (2017)

University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign

#### **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese

Native !!!!

Native | | | | |

Spanish

English

Advanced | | | | |

French

Beginner [ ] [ ] [ ]



## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Co-Founder

NMS - Sports Management

**1** 01/2016 - 04/2017

**9** United Arab Emirates

NMS has the mission of changing the way people look at physical activity and make it fun and enjoyable. With a fully digital experience, you can book your instructor for a personal class and pay online for it.

 Setting strategy, building e-commerce platform, building relationships with customers, hiring and training employees, keeping the books, and taking out the trash.

#### Sales Executive

Fitness First Middle East

**2014 - 2016** 

**♀** United Arab Emirates

World's leading health and fitness chains with over 60 clubs across 51 locations in the Middle East located in the UAE, Bahrain, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Kuwait and Located

Achieved 160% of my sales quota YoY and MVP for 3 quarters in a row

## Sales Executive

Decathlon Portugal

**2013 - 2014** 

**♀** Portugal

Decathlon designs, manufacture, and offer the best gear at the best prices for more than 80 sports.

 Part of the team that created the first Sports Camp by Decathlon at national level

#### Teacher

Minister of Education

**2013 - 2014** 

**♀** Portugal

**Public Primary School** 

• PE Teacher

## **VOLUNTEERING**

#### **Board Member**

Portuguese Business Council in Dubai

 The Portuguese Business Council (PBC) is an entity incorporated in May 2016 and registered with Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry with the purpose of improving the networking and business opportunities of Portuguese companies and individuals in the UAE in general, and Dubai in particular

## Handball Player

Dubai International Handball Club

**2014 - 2015** 

The first expats handball club in Dubai to participate in the national league

## Handball Player

Federação de Andebol de Portugal

**1993 - 2014** 

Around 21 years as federated handball athlete